<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on MBS</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on MBS</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 00:11:13 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>two calendars</title>
      <link>/posts/calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 00:11:13 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/calendar/</guid>
      <description>I follow two calendars since my childhood. (1) modern day solar calendar (gregorian) and (2) the lunar islamic calendar.
They have commonalities such they both are divided into 12 months although months have different days limit. For example, Moharram the first islamic month will have two fortnights which equals 28 days while the first the gregorian month january will have 31 days. This inequality increases the date difference of almost 12 days each year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>template-title</title>
      <link>/posts/slug/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 04:51:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/slug/</guid>
      <description>What is it?    How does it work?    Are you sure?    Can you do it?    Acknowledgments    Conclusions    References    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>life events</title>
      <link>/posts/life-events/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 02:26:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/life-events/</guid>
      <description>Tasks pending
 Tooba Shadi Hiba Shadi PhD     age events year     0 birth 1989   14 X 2006   16 XII 2006   17 BS 2007   21 BS 2011   21 ASE TRG 2011   22 Lecturer Sukkur IBA 2012   25 Lecturer Uni Sindh 2015   26 MS 2017   29 Asst: Prof Uni Sindh 2018   30 PhD ECU, Australia 2019   30 Married 2019   31 Father 2020   31 ECU Council Member 2020   32 Two Research Paper 2021   32 Data Scientist 2021   32 ECU Guild PG Officer, VP CAPA 2021   33 OxML, 5xMicrosoft, GSMIEEE, AACS 2022   *33 Second baby, 2xMicrosoft, MCT, MVP, CAR, 45L 2022    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a day</title>
      <link>/posts/a-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 01:18:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-day/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Items</title>
      <link>/posts/items/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:38:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/items/</guid>
      <description>My WooliesX Experience    Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m your author mbs today, I want to tell you about my recent Data Scientist job process with WooliesX. Btw this is my first time on stackedit and I’m loving it. 😍
Azure AI Engineer Certification    I passed my 5th Microsoft Azure Certification and I registered for 6th one.
Pie &amp;amp; AI Ambassador    I’m the official ambassador for Pie &amp;amp; AI in perth 😍</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Todo Marker</title>
      <link>/posts/todo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 21:06:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/todo/</guid>
      <description>Progress report submit
 prepare draft discuss with douglas submit on portal    MAiVAR Extended
 Add placeholders for extended results Get Ksounds results Get ESC50 results k400 results add those results to the manuscript    Survey 2
 Convert to TMM template Add subsection for CNN and Transformer based MMHAR Update Text in copied sections Discuss modalities in modality section with mathmatics (if possible)    Job</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Read1-Multimodal Action recognition in Compressed Video</title>
      <link>/posts/multimodal-har1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 19:34:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/multimodal-har1/</guid>
      <description>In this I will follow my preffered briefing method the WHAC method.
What?    Compressed video formats produced different modalities which includes i-frames, p-frames, b-frames and audio. A recent beautiful work from WACV 2022, produced fourtransformer-based architectures to fuse these four modalities in an interesting way.
Using the base Vit and ViViT models, MM-ViT scored better or equally nearby scores on UCF101, Kinetics 600 and SomethingSomethingv2 (without audio dataset).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>daily azkar</title>
      <link>/posts/dailyzikr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 20:39:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/dailyzikr/</guid>
      <description>Daily Azkar means the zikr that I should do on daily basis.
 First one is after fajar prayer.   After each prayer 33xSubhan Allah, 33xAlhamdulillah,34xAllah o Akbar.
  For increase in knowledge.
  A very powerful daily tasbeeh is 100 times Subhanallahi Wa bi hamdihi. Surah e Ikhlas equals one-third of Quran. Durood e Ibrahimi  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Early morning hike at King&#39;s Park</title>
      <link>/posts/kings-parks-hike/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 19:58:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/kings-parks-hike/</guid>
      <description>Today I woke up early around 6:30 and after morning prayers, I left for my much needed hike at King&amp;rsquo;s Park.
I arrived on time and met Damien, Peggy, Fred, a kenyan(don&amp;rsquo;t know the name) and Tim.
This route of the hike had downstream-ladders, a portion to hike uphill. walk across the bushes, passing nearby river, a beautiful paranomic view of Elizabeth Quay and Swan river. I felt quite after this hike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a typical friday</title>
      <link>/posts/friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 15:50:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/friday/</guid>
      <description>Yes a friday.
I wake up goto office. around juma prayer time i goto to prayer at mosque. i come back i spend time in office. i go back to asar maghrib isha i goto to home for dinner and sleep.
Technically, I should wake up at Fajar recite Surah e Yaseen, do ghusl, off to office then before juma prayer, I should recite Surah e Kahaf and then Juma prayer, return back to office and then off around Asar and Maghrib prayer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ashar- my son love &lt;3</title>
      <link>/posts/ashar/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 15:50:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ashar/</guid>
      <description>Ashar is a gift of Allah and an extreme blessing for the rest of my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Douglas- My PhD supervisor</title>
      <link>/posts/douglas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 15:50:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/douglas/</guid>
      <description>An excellent person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECU University Council</title>
      <link>/posts/council/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 15:50:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/council/</guid>
      <description>This is one of the amazing corporate experience, I have ever had so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saturday</title>
      <link>/posts/saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 15:50:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/saturday/</guid>
      <description>On saturday, I will work on my VCIP manuscript first and then I will finalize it for submission on monday.
Next I will resume ksounds work and try to extract results from ksounds. Once ksounds is done then move to k400 and get results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECU Guild</title>
      <link>/posts/hugo-coder/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 12:11:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hugo-coder/</guid>
      <description>ECU Guild is separate not for profit organization at my university. I currently work there is a head of postgraduate department who has 16 school reps from each school of ECU. I have to work 16 hours every fortnight for which there is some honorarium for me. I am also a senator which is by default if you are leading one of the business units, you become part of the senate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Coder theme</title>
      <link>/posts/ecu-guild/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 12:11:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ecu-guild/</guid>
      <description>Hi today, I want to talk about my interaction with hugo coder theme. I recently came across linkedin profile of a specialist data engineer, who is also instructor for some bootcamps and speaker at data related events. On his linkedin, he mentioned certain technologies which he uses for creating world class data architectures.
For everything, he shared his professional website url. I liked this idea of having a separate page on the web where you can simply talk about what you can offer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
