<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MBS</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on MBS</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 19:34:52 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 15:29:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Bilal, currenlty based in Perth and my hometown is shahdadpur, a small city in Pakistan.
Languages : Marwari, Urdu, Sindhi, English
 Anything in brain is not real.
 Action and existance is the real happening.
  Presentations Talks and Events:     &amp;lsquo;Journey with Python for a Data Scientist&amp;rsquo;, Python WA, Riff,45 St George Terrace, Perth , WA 2nd Dec 2021 slides DSB 2022 ECU Research Presentation, Pan Pacific Hotel Deeplearning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 15:32:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/updates/</guid>
      <description>This page follows chronological order, i.e., the newest item comes first.
Upcoming    WACV 2023    Date: 4-7 Jan, 2023
1st round Deadline: 13 July 2022
2nd round Deadline: 29 August 2022
Mode: ?
Venue: ?
ACCV 2022    Date: 4-8 Dec, 2022
Venue: Macua, China
Deadline: 6 July 2022 11:59 Pacific ST
Mode: ?
35th AJCAI 2022    Date: 5-8 Dec, 2022</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Read1-Multimodal Action recognition in Compressed Video</title>
      <link>/posts/multimodal-har1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 19:34:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/multimodal-har1/</guid>
      <description>In this I will follow my preffered briefing method the WHAC method.
What?    Compressed video formats produced different modalities which includes i-frames, p-frames, b-frames and audio. A recent beautiful work from WACV 2022, produced fourtransformer-based architectures to fuse these four modalities in an interesting way.
Using the base Vit and ViViT models, MM-ViT scored better or equally nearby scores on UCF101, Kinetics 600 and SomethingSomethingv2 (without audio dataset).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>daily azkar</title>
      <link>/posts/dailyzikr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 20:39:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/dailyzikr/</guid>
      <description>Daily Azkar means the zikr that I should do on daily basis.
 First one is after fajar prayer.   After each prayer 33xSubhan Allah, 33xAlhamdulillah,34xAllah o Akbar.
  For increase in knowledge.
  A very powerful daily tasbeeh is 100 times Subhanallahi Wa bi hamdihi. Surah e Ikhlas equals one-third of Quran. Durood e Ibrahimi  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECU Guild</title>
      <link>/posts/hugo-coder/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 12:11:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hugo-coder/</guid>
      <description>ECU Guild is separate not for profit organization at my university. I currently work there is a head of postgraduate department who has 16 school reps from each school of ECU. I have to work 16 hours every fortnight for which there is some honorarium for me. I am also a senator which is by default if you are leading one of the business units, you become part of the senate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Coder theme</title>
      <link>/posts/ecu-guild/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 12:11:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ecu-guild/</guid>
      <description>Hi today, I want to talk about my interaction with hugo coder theme. I recently came across linkedin profile of a specialist data engineer, who is also instructor for some bootcamps and speaker at data related events. On his linkedin, he mentioned certain technologies which he uses for creating world class data architectures.
For everything, he shared his professional website url. I liked this idea of having a separate page on the web where you can simply talk about what you can offer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>  Have any question you want answered?   Have a project or startup you would like to work on together?  Just use the form below to reach to me. Name    Your email     Message    Send   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
